(Penny:)and all she did was help
out another scientist,
(Penny:)I'm thinking you might
have to let this one go.
Ugh, "let it go."
(Sheldon:)I have heard that
my whole life.
(Sheldon:)Every time something upsets me
somebody says, "let it go,"
(Sheldon:)you know,
like it's my fault,
(Sheldon:)and it's not okay
to feel the way I feel.
(sighs) I don't know
what to tell you.
(Penny:)I mean, why don't
you talk to her?
(Sheldon:)Is that all you have?
(Sheldon:)Shopworn tidbits like
"talk to her" and "let it go"?
(Sheldon:)Gee, Penny,
life's giving me lemons.
(Sheldon:)What should I do?
(Penny:)Well, you could shove
them somewhere.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now you're
getting creative.
(Barry:)Thanks again
for your help.
(Leonard:)No problem.
Our pleasure.
(Leonard:)The place really
looks great.
(Raj:)Yeah, you should have
burned it down years ago.
(Stuart:)I keep telling you
I didn't burn it down.
(Leonard:)We know, we know--
because burning something down
(Leonard:)for the insurance money
is a "crime."
(Bernadette:)Stuart, this place
looks amazing.
(chuckles)
Thanks.
(Howard:)You really did
a nice job.
(Stuart:)And thank you
for putting up with me